Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-086
  - Drugs (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Vietnam (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Irvine (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - SCIRE Personnel, Dana Weigant, Joy Clemens (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Prime Student Notes (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Prime Faculty Notes (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Prime Proposals (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Prime Publicity and Mailings (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Prime, Proposals Larsen 1990 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Prime, Prosposals, File, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - Prime Bartling, Holly (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Prime, Flowers, Chris (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - Prime, Gence, Michelle (Box 49, Folder 55)
  - Prime, Lim, Jane (Box 49, Folder 56)
  - Prime Ogunji, Natasha (Box 49, Folder 57)
  - Prime, Sekaquaptewa, Pat (Box 49, Folder 58)
  - Prime Tsai, Jeanna (Box 49, Folder 59)
  - Prime, Tseng, Jennifer (Box 49, Folder 60)
  - Prime Faculty (Box 49, Folder 61)
  - Prime Students (Box 49, Folder 62)
  - 590 A Memorabilia (Box 49, Folder 63)
  - Clippings to 1974 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles to 1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI Clippings 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings: 1978-1979 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings on Social and Political Issues (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - SWOPSI Related Newspaper Clippings 1979-1980 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Daily Articles on SWOPSI (1980-1981) (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Daily/SWOPSI 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI Related Newspaper Clippings 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - SWOPSI Related News Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - SWOPSI Related News Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - SWOPSI Related News Clippings 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - SWOPSI Related News Clippings 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - IAC Clippings/ News Stories 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Press Clippings: 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Misc. Articles (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - End Quarter Reports Fall 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - End Quarter Reports Winter 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - End Quarter Reports, Spring 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Grades, Fall 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Grades Winter 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Grades Spring 1980-1981 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Grades Fall 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Grades Winter 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Grades Spring 1981-1982 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Grades, Fall 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Grades, Winter 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Grades, Spring 1982-1983 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Grades Fall 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Grades, Winter 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Grades Spring 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Grades Fall 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Grades Winter 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Grades Spring 1984-1985 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Growing Up Female, UGS 065 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - The Peace Corps in Africa, Three Case Studies (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - Blacks on Sex and the Catholic Church (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - UGS 95 Pre-Columbian Art, Glen Brown, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - SWOPSI 102 Kujichaqulia, Marchella Jones, Rebecca Schanberg, Group 2 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - SWOPSI 102 Kujichaqulia, Marie Bui, Ryan Fitzpatrick, group 3 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - SWOPSI 102 Kujichaqulia, Vanessa Henlon, Bruno Lewin, group 4 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - SWOPSI 102 Kujichaqulia, Trevor Brown, Bikku Kuruvila, Jonah Petchesky, group 5 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - SWOPSI 102 Kujichaqulia, Margaret Solomon, Cindi Moothart, group 6 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - SWOPSE 102, Kim Bluitt, Jay Tucker, Robert Gross, Heather Willens, Kujichaqulia, group 7 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 124, Medicine and Law (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - SWOPSI 142 The Intifada (Box 50, Folder 47)
  - SWOPSI 182 The Iran Contra Affair, Larry Bensky, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 48)
  - SWOPSI 184 The Death Penalty, Kornblith/Sontag, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  - SWOPSI 186 Drug Abuse and Prevention, Li Miao, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  - Project to Incorporate Multiculturalism in the Psychology of Women, Spring 1990 (Box 50, Folder 51)
  - Alli List (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - Child-Rearing, Values and "Outcomes" East and West. What Can We Learn from Other Cultures?, 3/20/91 (Box 50, Folder 52)
  - SWOPSI Student Reports (Box 50, Folder 53)
  - Martha Cocke, UGS 61, Fall 1988 (Box 50, Folder 54)
  - Brad Johnson, UGS 61, Fall 1988 (Box 50, Folder 55)
  - Mark T. Seielstad, UGS 61, Fall 1988 (Box 50, Folder 56)
  - David Steinmiller UGS 61 Fall 1988 (Box 50, Folder 57)
  - Rick Wolfgram, UGS 61, Fall 1988 (Box 50, Folder 58)
  - Stanford Coalition Against Apartheid 1985 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - PC 746 UGS 56 (Ward) Spring 1990 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI 302 attn: E. Yuen and N. Netherland (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - UGS/SWOPSI 3092, Attn: Prof. Noriega Winter 1990 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Course Reader Materials: The 60's and Beyond (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Research Handbook for Southeast Asian Amecian Materials 1990 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Mideast Reader, January 22-23 1991 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Mideast Reader, January 22-23 1991 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI 11, Reproductive Right and Wrongs Winter 1991 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - SWOPSI 197 Winter 1991 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Economics 118 The Economics of Development Spring 1991 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - SWOPSI Procedure Manual Porgram Assistant (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Black Untitled Folder (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - CIV Clippings 1986-1987 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - CIV Clippings 1988-1989 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Telephone Notes and Index Cards (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - SCTR124 Police: A closer look (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - PB Editorial Policy (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Course Lists 1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 152 Androgyny Theme House Spring 1977 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - PB Public Events and Course Expense Policy (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - PB Guidelines 78 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Policy Board Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Policy Board Information, 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Policy Board Mailings 1982-1983 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Policy Board 1983-1984 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Policy Board Schedules (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Policy Board Members 1984 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Policy Board Minutes 1984 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Freshman/ Sophomore Seminar Papers (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Freshman/ Sophomore Seminars Summer (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Policy Board Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Policy Board Mailings 1984-1985 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Suggested Policy Board Members (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - IAC Publicity Mailing List (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Turnaround Presonnel Forms from IAC Instructors (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Freshman/ Sophomore Seminar Progress (Winkler File) (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - IAC Policy Board 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Fall Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Winter Quarter 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - IAC Catalogue Spring 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - FSS 011 Policy Analysis in Poor Countries Winter 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - IAC 147 Fall 1986 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - IAC Courses Communication with Accreditation Committee (Winklerfile) (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Fall 1967-1987 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Winter 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Spring 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Summary of IAC Courses Fall 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - IAC Winter Quarter, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - IAC Spring Quarter 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - FSS Fall 1987 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - FSS 1 Breakthroughs and Innovations in Science and Technology, Fall Quarter 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - FSS 3 Human Subjects in Medical Experimentation, Fall Quarter 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - FSS 6 Nutrition: Fact and Fancy Winter Quarter 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - FSS12 New Psychtherapeutic Approaches to Addiction, Spring Quarter 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - IAC Fall Quarter 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - IAC Winter Quarter Courses, 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Fall 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Winter 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Spring 1987-1988 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - FSS001: Science and Technology, Breakthroughs and Innovations, Fall Quarter 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - FSS009: Breakthrough: Emerging New Thinking, Fall Quarter 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - FSS007: Policy Anaylsis of Developing Countries, Winter Quarter 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - FSS014 Theater and Politics, Winter Quarter 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - FSS 008: Artificial People... Spring Quarter 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - FSS 15: Interactions Between Science and Christianity Spring Quarter 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Fall 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Winter 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Spring 1988-1989 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - Fall 1989-1990 (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Saving IAC 1992-Fall 1991 (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Freshman/ Sophomore Seminars (Box 53, Folder 56)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1992-144
  - Budget records, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Health Psychology class - student papers, 1991-92 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - IAC catalogs 1986-87 (Fall, Winter) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - IAC catalogs 1987-88 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - IAC catalogs 1988-89 (Autumn, Winter) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - IAC catalogs 1989-90 (Fall, Winter) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - IAC catalogs 1990-91 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - IAC catalogs 1991-92 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Peter Faulkner Memorial Fund, 1988-89 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of catalog covers (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - SWOPSI course lists 1975-80 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - SWOPSI 101, Fall 1987, class proposal (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - UGS 87 (India) - student paper 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous course descriptions, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Posters, 1978-85 and undated (Box 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1995-011
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2006-290
  - Dr. Kathy Cohen's Study of Undergraduate Specials: binder of documents from 1960s with her introductory sheets, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)